<notes createdt="周四, 9 5月 2024 2:56 下午" selectednoteindex="1" showlinenumbers="N" toolbarlocation="0" fontname="ArialMT" fontsize="12" wordwrap="N" fontColorDefault="N" fontColorRed="0" fontColorGreen="0" fontColorBlue="0" bgColorDefault="N" bgColorRed="255" bgColorGreen="255" bgColorBlue="255" bgLineColorShow="N" bgLineColorDefault="N" bgLineColorRed="255" bgLineColorGreen="255" bgLineColorBlue="255" lineNumberColorDefault="N" lineNumberColorRed="255" lineNumberColorGreen="255" lineNumberColorBlue="255">
  <note title="N" createdt="周四, 9 5月 2024 2:56 下午">1. accept (接受) [əkˈsept]
I accept your apology.
He accepted the job offer.
2. busy (忙碌) [ˈbɪzi]
I'm too busy to talk right now.
The restaurant is always busy at lunchtime.
3. clear (清楚) [klɪər]
I need clear instructions on how to get there.
The sky is clear today.
4. deliver (交付) [dɪˈlɪvər]
The package was delivered this morning.
He delivered a powerful speech at the conference.
5. easy (简单) [ˈiːzi]
This game is really easy.
He finds math easy.
6. forget (忘记) [fəˈɡet]
Don't forget to lock the door.
I forgot her birthday.
7. guess (猜) [ɡes]
I guess you’re right.
Let me guess what happened.
8. help (帮助) [help]
Can you help me with these boxes?
She always helps those in need.
9. introduce (介绍) [ˌɪn.trəˈduːs]
Let me introduce you to my colleague.
He introduced a new idea at the meeting.
10. joke (玩笑) [dʒoʊk]
He told a funny joke.
It’s just a joke, don’t take it seriously.
11. know (知道) [noʊ]
I know what to do.
Do you know her?
12. learn (学习) [lɜːrn]
I'm learning to play the guitar.
We learn from our mistakes.
13. move (移动) [muːv]
Could you move your car, please?
He moved to a new city for his job.
14. need (需要) [niːd]
I need some advice.
You need to see this.
15. open (打开) [ˈoʊpən]
Please open the window.
The store opens at nine.
16. play (玩) [pleɪ]
Let's play a game.
He plays football on weekends.
17. quick (快) [kwɪk]
Give me a quick response.
He's a quick learner.
18. read (读) [riːd]
I love to read before bed.
Read the instructions carefully.
19. speak (说话) [spiːk]
He speaks three languages.
Speak louder, please.
20. travel (旅行) [ˈtrævəl]
I travel to Europe every year.
She travels frequently for work.
21. understand (理解) [ˌʌn.dərˈstænd]
I don't understand what you mean.
He understands the importance of being punctual.
22. visit (访问) [ˈvɪz.ɪt]
We plan to visit our relatives this weekend.
Have you visited the new museum?
23. want (想要) [wɒnt]
I want a cup of coffee.
She wants to become a doctor.
24. x-ray (reɪ]) [ˈeks
He had an x-ray to check for broken bones.
X-ray technology is vital for medical diagnosis.
25. yes (是的) [jes]
Yes, I agree with you.
Yes, that sounds like a good idea.
26. zone (区域) [zoʊn]
We are entering a residential zone.
Please stay in the safety zone.
27. apologize (道歉) [əˈpɒl.ə.dʒaɪz]
I apologize for any inconvenience caused.
She apologized for arriving late.
28. behave (行为) [bɪˈheɪv]
Please behave yourself at the party.
The children behaved well in the restaurant.
29. careful (小心) [ˈkeə.fʊl]
Be careful when you cross the street.
She is careful with her words.
30. discuss (讨论) [dɪˈskʌs]
Let's discuss the project details tomorrow.
They discussed their plans for the future.
31. enjoy (享受) [ɪnˈdʒɔɪ]
I enjoy reading books in my free time.
They really enjoyed their vacation.
32. fix (修理) [fɪks]
Can you fix this broken chair?
He fixed the leak in the pipe.
33. give (给) [ɡɪv]
Give me a call when you arrive.
She gave him a birthday gift.
34. happy (快乐) [ˈhæp.i]
I'm happy to hear you're doing well.
She feels happy when she is with her family.
35. invite (邀请) [ɪnˈvaɪt]
We invited all our friends to our wedding.
He was invited to join the committee.
36. jump (跳跃) [dʒʌmp]
The cat jumped onto the table.
Children love to jump in puddles.
37. keep (保持) [kiːp]
Keep the door closed.
She keeps her room very tidy.
38. leave (离开) [liːv]
Please don't leave me alone here.
He left the company after ten years.
39. mention (提到) [ˈmen.ʃən]
Did she mention anything about me?
Don't mention it to anyone.
40. offer (提供) [ˈɒf.ər]
He offered to help us with the move.
The company offered me a new position.
41. promise (承诺) [ˈprɒm.ɪs]
I promise to call you tonight.
She made a promise to keep his secret.
42. question (问题) [ˈkwes.tʃən]
If you have any questions, feel free to ask.
He raised a question during the meeting.
43. respect (尊重) [rɪˈspekt]
I have great respect for his work.
Respect others' opinions even if you disagree.
44. share (分享) [ʃeər]
She shared her snacks with everyone.
Can you share your thoughts on this matter?
45. talk (谈话) [tɔːk]
We need to talk about your performance.
He talks too much during class.
46. under (在...之下) [ˈʌn.dər]
The cat hid under the table.
We sat under a tree to avoid the sun.
47. view (视图，看法) [vjuː]
We have a beautiful view of the lake from our house.
I'd like to hear your views on this topic.
48. write (写) [raɪt]
Please write your name here.
She writes a blog about her travels.
49. xenophobia (仇外，排外) [ˌzen.əˈfəʊ.bi.ə]
Xenophobia is a serious issue in diverse societies.
The campaign aims to fight xenophobia and promote tolerance.
50. yawn (打哈欠) [jɔːn]
He tried to suppress a yawn during the meeting.
Yawning is often contagious.
51. zeal (热情) [ziːl]
She pursued her studies with great zeal.
His zeal for reform was noticeable.
52. adapt (适应) [əˈdæpt]
You need to adapt to the new working conditions.
Species that adapt well to their environment thrive.
53. break (打破) [breɪk]
Don't break the glass!
She took a break from work to travel the world.
54. carry (携带) [ˈkæ.ri]
Please carry your ID at all times.
He carries the responsibility for the team's success.
55. drive (驾驶) [draɪv]
He drives to work every day.
She has a long drive ahead of her.
56. examine (检查) [ɪɡˈzæm.ɪn]
The doctor examined the patient carefully.
We need to examine all possibilities before making a decision.
57. fill (填充) [fɪl]
Please fill in the form and return it to us.
He filled the glass with water.
58. grow (生长) [ɡroʊ]
The plant grows quickly in the summer.
Her interest in art has grown over the years.
59. hold (握住) [hoʊld]
Hold the handrail while going down the stairs.
Can you hold my bag for a moment?
60. join (加入) [dʒɔɪn]
She decided to join the club.
You should join us for dinner.
61. laugh (笑) [læf]
We couldn't help but laugh at the joke.
She laughed at the funny scene in the movie.
62. notice (注意) [ˈnoʊ.tɪs]
Did you notice the error in the report?
She noticed he was looking tired.
63. open (打开) [ˈoʊ.pən]
Please open the window.
The store opens at eight o'clock.
64. push (推) [pʊʃ]
Push the door to open it.
He pushed the car because it wouldn't start.
65. take (拿) [teɪk]
Take an umbrella, it might rain later.
She took the book from the shelf.
66. wait (等待) [weɪt]
Wait here while I get the car.
We had to wait an hour for the next train.
67. explain (解释) [ɪkˈspleɪn]
Please explain how this machine works.
He explained the rules to the new players.
68. yearn (渴望) [jɜːrn]
She yearned for a chance to prove herself.
He yearned to return to his homeland.
69. zip (拉链) [zɪp]
Zip up your jacket, it's cold outside.
He zipped the tent flap closed.
70. adjust (调整) [əˈdʒʌst]
Adjust the volume so everyone can hear.
He adjusted his tie before the interview.
71. bake (烘焙) [beɪk]
She baked a cake for his birthday.
We're baking cookies this afternoon.
72. call (呼叫) [kɔːl]
Call me when you arrive.
He called to say he would be late.
73. develop (发展) [dɪˈvel.əp]
She developed a new technique for solving the problem.
The story develops slowly at first.
74. eat (吃) [iːt]
We eat breakfast at 7 a.m. every day.
What did you eat for dinner last night?
75. find (找到) [faɪnd]
I can't find my keys anywhere.
He found a new job in the city.
76. improve (改进) [ɪmˈpruːv]
She has significantly improved her English.
We are always looking to improve our services.
77. walk (走路) [wɔːk]
Let's walk to the park.
She walks her dog every morning.
78. create (创造) [kriːˈeɪt]
She likes to create her own recipes.
The new policy will create more jobs.
79. show (显示) [ʃəʊ]
She showed me her wedding photos.
The guide will show us around the museum.
80. send (发送) [send]
Send me an email with the details.
He sent a package to his family.
81. change (改变) [tʃeɪndʒ]
She changed her appointment to Tuesday.
Can you change a twenty-dollar bill?
82. increase (增加) [ɪnˈkriːs]
We've seen an increase in sales this month.
They plan to increase the number of employees.
83. find (发现) [faɪnd]
Did you find what you were looking for?
She found a rare book at the store.
84. seem (看起来) [siːm]
It seems like a good idea.
She seems happy today.
85. include (包括) [ɪnˈkluːd]
The price includes taxes and service charges.
Your responsibilities include managing the team.
86. achieve (实现) [əˈtʃiːv]
She achieved her goal of running a marathon.
The project achieved great success.
87. consider (考虑) [kənˈsɪdər]
Consider all the options before making a decision.
He is considering moving to a new city.
88. require (需要) [rɪˈkwaɪər]
This job requires a lot of travel.
You are required to wear a uniform.
89. attend (参加) [əˈtend]
She attends a dance class every week.
Many people attended the conference.
90. practice (练习) [ˈpræk.tɪs]
He practices the violin every day.
They have soccer practice three times a week.
91. receive (接收) [rɪˈsiːv]
Did you receive the letter I sent?
She received an award for her work.
92. save (保存) [seɪv]
Save your work frequently to avoid losing data.
He's saving money to buy a house.
93. support (支持) [səˈpɔːrt]
I'll support you no matter what.
The beams support the weight of the roof.
94. destroy (破坏) [dɪˈstrɔɪ]
The fire destroyed the entire building.
The virus can destroy data on your computer.
95. cover (覆盖) [ˈkʌv.ər]
Cover the pot while the soup cooks.
The insurance policy covers damage from natural disasters.
96. apply (应用，申请) [əˈplaɪ]
She applied for a new passport.
You need to apply the cream twice a day.
97. avoid (避免) [əˈvɔɪd]
Avoid eating too much sugar.
He avoided answering my question.
98. behave (表现) [bɪˈheɪv]
The children behaved very well at the dinner.
How does the machine behave under extreme conditions?
99. connect (连接) [kəˈnekt]
Please connect the printer to the computer.
I feel a strong connection with nature.
100. contact (联系) [ˈkɒntækt]
Please contact customer service for assistance.
He lost contact with his friends from college.
101. deliver (递送) [dɪˈlɪvər]
The postman delivered the letters this morning.
She delivered a powerful speech at the conference.
102. earn (赚得) [ɜːrn]
He earns a good salary at his new job.
She earned respect through hard work.
103. emphasize (强调) [ˈemfəsaɪz]
The teacher emphasized the importance of reading.
I want to emphasize how critical this project is.
104. enhance (提高) [ɪnˈhɑːns]
This software enhances productivity.
Adding salt can enhance the flavor of the dish.
105. ensure (确保) [ɪnˈʃʊər]
Ensure all windows are locked before leaving.
The contract ensures that he will be paid monthly.
106. establish (建立) [ɪˈstæblɪʃ]
The company was established in 1980.
We need to establish some basic rules.
107. evaluate (评估) [ɪˈvæljueɪt]
It's important to evaluate your options.
The manager will evaluate the employees' performance.
108. feature (特征) [ˈfiːtʃər]
The new model features several improvements.
This phone has many unique features.
109. gather (收集) [ˈɡæðər]
We gathered information for our project.
The family gathers every year for Thanksgiving.
110. handle (处理) [ˈhændl]
She handled the situation very well.
This case is being handled by our best lawyer.
111. improve (改善) [ɪmˈpruːv]
He improved his skills with practice.
We're working to improve our customer service.
112. maintain (维持) [meɪnˈteɪn]
It's important to maintain a healthy diet.
She maintained her composure in a difficult situation.
113. negotiate (谈判) [nɪˈɡəʊʃieɪt]
They negotiated a new contract.
We need to negotiate the terms of the agreement.
114. operate (操作) [ˈɒpəreɪt]
She learned to operate the new software quickly.
The business operates in three countries.</note>
  <note title="S" createdt="周五, 10 5月 2024 5:20 下午" />
</notes>